let's go over inheritance in solidity in
让我们在这个视频军号中仔细研究一下继承，
this video bugle with a case where a
contract and here it's a single parent
合同，这里是单亲文化，例如合同可以继承
culture for example contract be inherits
a parent contract a and we're not going
父合同a，我们不处理合同B
to deal with the case where contract B
inherits from two parents contract C and
从两个父合同C和D继承
contract D multiple inheritance will be
the topic of the next video so let's see
下一个视频的主题，让我们来看一些混音示例，我们将继续
some examples in remix so we'll go over
the basic syntax for inheritance and go
继承的基本语法，并介绍一些继承的示例
over some examples of inherited
functions next we'll go over how to
函数接下来，我们将探讨如何覆盖继承的函数
override inherited functions I'll also
show you examples of how to pass
向您展示如何将参数传递给父构造函数的示例
parameters to parent constructors we
will consider two situations when the
当我们传递给父级的参数时，将考虑两种情况
parameter that we pass into the parent
constructor is fixed and the case when
构造函数是固定的，当我们传递给
the parameter that we pass into the
parent constructor is not fixed first
首先不固定父构造函数，让我们回顾一下继承的语法
let's go over the syntax for inheritance
we want contract B to inherit from
我们希望合同B从合同a继承，换句话说，合同a是
contract a in other words contract a is
the parent of contract B let's say we
合同B的父级假设我们在合同a中有一个函数
have a function in contract a that we
also want in contract B for this example
对于此示例，合同B也需要在合同内创建函数
like created a function inside contract
a that returns the name of the contract
返回合同名称的合同B可以继承
contract B can inherit the
functionalities of contract a by using
使用关键字is和其后跟名称的合约a的功能
the keyword is and followed by the name
of the contract in this case a go ahead
在这种情况下，合同的执行将继续进行，并编译和部署合同B
and compile and deploy contract B
click on the deployed contract and you
单击已部署的合同，您可以在此处看到该合同被继承
can see here the contract be inherited
the functioning get contract name from
功能自合同日起获取合同名称，执行该功能并
contract day execute the function and
you can verify that the function inside
您可以验证合同日期之内的函数是否已被调用接下来我们开始
contract day was called next let's go
over how to override functions from a
有关如何从父合约覆盖功能的问题，请先复制该功能
parent contract first copy the function
from contract a into contract B we want
从合同a到合同B，我们希望此函数返回不同的值
this function to return a different
value from the function inside contract
合约a中函数的值，因此您将返回值更改为
a so you'll change the return value to
contract B recompile and redeploy
合同B重新编译和重新部署合同B
contract B
once the new contract is deployed go
一旦部署了新合同，就继续执行该功能
ahead and execute the function get
contract name you can see here that the
合同名称，您可以在此处看到该函数返回字符串合同B
function return the string contract B
this shows that the function we wrote
这表明我们编写的函数取代了父函数的一件事
overrode the parent function one thing
you need to be careful here is that the
您需要注意的是，合同的功能签名和
function signature for the contract and
the parent contract has to be the same
父合同必须是相同的，例如在这里我稍微改变了
for example here I slightly changed the
function to taking a parameter after you
重新编译和重新部署合同后获取参数的函数
recompile and redeploy the contract
you'll notice that contract B has two
您会注意到合约B有两个功能，它没有覆盖
functions and it did not overwrite the
function from contract a so when you
合约a的功能，因此当您想要从合约a覆盖功能时
want to overwrite a function from a
parent contract make sure to match the
父合同确保与功能签名完全匹配
function signature as exactly as it is
so next that's not about how to pass
所以接下来的内容与如何将参数传递给父构造函数无关
parameters into a parent constructor
first contract a has a constructor that
第一个合约a有一个以名称为参数的构造函数，
takes in the name as parameter and
stores it as a state variable one way to
将其存储为状态变量的一种将参数传递给父构造函数的方法
pass parameters to a parent constructor
is like this another way is like this
就像这样，另一种方式是这样，如果你需要传递变量
and if you need to pass variable
parameters to the pen constructor this
笔构造函数的参数，这就是您的工作方式，让我们部署它
is how you do it let's deploy this
contract and see an example called
合约，并看到一个称为传递合约B并带有双引号的示例，例如
passing contract B with double quotes as
parameter to the constructor of contract
合同B的构造函数的参数，然后点击deploy点击deploy
B and hit deploy click on the deploy
contract and click on the function name
合同，然后单击函数名称，您应该获得合同，所以该怎么办？
you should get contract be back so what
just happened here was that we passed in
只是这里发生的是我们将参数合约B传递给了
the parameter contract B to the
constructor of contract B next step
合同B下一步的构造函数的参数已传递到
parameter was passed into the
constructor of contract a the
合同的建设者a合同的建设者a
constructor contract a took that
parameter and then set it to its state
参数，然后将其设置为其状态变量
variable
in this video we went over how to
在本视频中，我们介绍了如何继承单亲合同以及如何继承
inherit single-parent contracts and how
to pass parameters to parent
在下一个视频中将参数传递给父构造函数
constructors in the next video we'll go
over multiple inheritance and how to
多重继承以及如何调用父合同非常感谢
call parent contracts thank you so much
for watching and I'll talk to you soon
观看，我会尽快与您联系